

# Janki Kansagara

Sr. Software Engineer

+916352058420

# Rajkot, India

# **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

I am a Senior iOS Developer with over 7+ years of expertise, specializing in the design, development, and testing of iOS applications within the On-Demand Delivery, Transportation, Warehouse Management System (WMS), Telecommunications, E-commerce, and ERP domains. My focus has been on crafting robust solutions for iOS platforms, catering to a user base in the millions.

Throughout my career, I have been actively engaged in managing various overseas enterprise projects, necessitating consistent client communication and the implementation of continuous integration and delivery practices. I excel as a team player, demonstrating proficiency in both collaborative team environments and self-directed settings.

# DIGITAL SKILLS

- iOS App Development : IOS / Swift / objective-C / Swift UI / Cocoa touch / UIKit / Firebase / Core data / Core location / Core Bluetooth / APNS / Google map Apis / Cloud Messaging / Rx Swift / Multi Threading Programming / Postman
- CI/CD pipelines: Jenkins/ Sonar/ AWS Device Farm/ GitHub Actions
- Agile Project/Task Management System: Source Tree / Jira / Trello / Git
- Software Development Methodology: Scrum / Waterfall / Agile

# WORK EXPERIENCE

Present

# 2021 - Present Senior Software Engineer | KiwiTech | Noida-Delhi . India

I joined Kiwitech as a Senior Software Engineer, I'm working here on NYC based client project called MSR, Bar-i currently as a Lead developer. My major role is to develop functionalities with expected outcome, maintaining code structure, develop reliable and robust app, guide other developers through the whole process of development and maintain product quality.

https://www.kiwitech.com/

2020 - 2021

#### Senior Software Engineer | Elluminati Inc | Rajkot, India 1 Years

I joined Elluminati Inc. as a Senior Software Engineer, I worked here as a Lead developer for On-Demand Delivery, Service provider and Taxi apps. As it is a product based company, I Played a major role in discussing the enhancements and implementing them with team. I got a chance to develop apps from scratch and to help team to develop products which has thousands of users.

https://www.elluminatiinc.com/

2019 - 2020

1 Years

# Senior Software Engineer | Softeaven Solutions | Rajkot, India

Softeaven is a startup company working on mainly e-commerce projects, I worked on Payment gateways, GCM, Beacons, GeoFecing. I am directly interacting with the Clients for requirement gathering and make those requirements working in smooth and efficient way.

https://www.softeaven.com/

2019 - 2019

3 Months

#### Software Engineer | Panamax Inc. | Ahmedabad , India

Panamax Inc. the technology arm of Bankai Group, where I worked as an SE, my key role 1s to deliver the quality product to FinTech and telecommunication technologies.

# LANGUAGE SKILLS

English Hindi Gujarati

# Links

https://in.linkedin.com/jan-ki-kansagara

had also worked on React Native as well for short period of time to make Hybrid apps to work on any platforms. My role of concentration is to optimize, develop & enhance features and make them work with their millions of users. https://www.panamaxil.com/

2017 - 2018

1 Years

## Software Engineer | Value Chain Solutions | Ahmedabad , India

Value Chain Solutions is a product based company (CMMI 2), here my major role was to develop and maintain a Pharma Reporting Software System, MR Reporting System, WMS. I've been a part of big team here and working efficiently as a team player and a developer. https://www.ecubix.com/

2015 - 2017

2 Years

# Associate Software Engineer | Tatvsoft | Ahmedabad , India

Tatvasoft is one of the leading global custom software development company. I worked as a trainee + ASE here. My major role was to learn new technologies and make them functional with any project. I've also been trained to have calls with clients and provide them services with they have aimed for.

https://www.tatvasoft.com/

# **EDUCATION**

2011 - 2015

4 Years

Bachelor Engineering in Information and Technology | Gujarat Technological University | Rajkot, India

Secured: 8.51 CGPA

# **PROJECTS**

## Bar-i | Bar Inventory Management System

Role: Senior Software Engineer

**Domain:** Bar Inventory Management System

**Brief**: Here I am working as a Senior software engineer. This bar inventory project provides the services to manage/count all the alcohol bottles/vessels in a Bar in fastest way, It works on both online and offline mode. Includes hardware integrations like Vessel barcode scanner, weighing machine to weight and add items in records to update stock accordingly.

Technology: Swift 5.5, CI/CD, JSON (for Rest-API

communication), Git

https://apps.apple.com/us/app/bar-i/id1546042570

#### Measure protocol(MSR) | Surveys & Rewards

Role: Senior Software Engineer

Domain: Surveys & Rewards

**Brief**: Measure protocol has different types of social, entertainment, market trends, app reviews related survey & reward app which is used to empower marketing, product and insights professionals to drive brand success through data driven decisions. Users are given facility to redeem MSR points for different coupons and vouchers. I had worked as a lead developer for this project.

Technology: Swift 5.5, CI/CD, JSON (for Rest-API

communication), Git

https://apps.apple.com/gb/app/msr-surveys-rewards/id1450536498

#### **EDelivery | Food Delivery System**

Role: Senior Software Engineer

Domain: Food Delivery System

**Brief**: Here I am working as a Senior Software Engineer for Food, Other services provider project. Our app handling thousands of Bookings daily so my responsibility includes the

optimization, stability and scalability of the application.

Technology: Swift 5.0, CI/CD, JSON (for Rest-API

communication), Git

https://apps.apple.com/us/app/elluminati-delivery-store/id6466286247

#### Eber | Taxi Service App

Role: Senior Software Engineer

Domain: Taxi Service App

**Brief**: Here I am working as a Senior Software Engineer for Taxi services provider project. Which includes User, driver apps. Our app handling thousands of Bookings daily. so my responsibility includes the optimization, stability and scalability of the application.

Technology: Swift 5.0, CI/CD, JSON (for

Rest-API communication), Git

https://apps.apple.com/us/app/eber-client/id1184832545

#### Hello Sitter | Baby Sitting App

Role: Software Engineer

Domain: Baby Sitting App

**Brief:** HS is a babysitting application to book sitters in US.It includes booking of best matched sitter and serves many clients for particular hours.I was working as SE and my role was to review detailed requirements and develop stable application and optimize code.

Technology: Swift 5.0, CI/CD, JSON (for Rest-API

communication), Git

https://apps.apple.com/us/app/hello-sitter-childcare/id1078973005